<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on amar</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on amar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:13:44 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alternative Sources</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/alternative-sources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:13:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/alternative-sources/</guid><description>Some notes from a k20 6speed transmission refurbishment, this car was made in 2002, it is now the end of 2025. We pulled this apart so we can install a Cusco LSD into the unit. While this is removed I intend to replace whatever is ruined.
Before pulling this out, I had noticed some notchyness when shifting between 1st-&amp;gt;2nd, as well as the 3rd gear popping out of gear when on track.</description></item><item><title>Removing Barriers</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/removing-barriers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:20:12 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/removing-barriers/</guid><description>One of the nice things about LLMs and their ability to &amp;ldquo;program&amp;rdquo; things is that it really make it easier to iterate and test out ideas for small applications. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using LLMs on and off in order to figure out where in my workflow these tools have a place (and where to not include them at all). When kept on a short leash, they c16:18an rapidly remove barriers to creating applications for personal use.</description></item><item><title>writing a good issue</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/writing-a-good-issue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 23:38:49 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/writing-a-good-issue/</guid><description>What is it? Issues are a starting point for a observed problem with software.
What makes a bad issue? Bad issues can be incomplete, difficult to follow, or don&amp;rsquo;t clearly express the problem at hand.
What makes a good issue? Keep it structured. Give all the details (starting from the top). Make it easier to navigate the issue (use Markdown). Give some attention to formatting text (capitalization, etc). Structure the problem clearly (make it easier to follow).</description></item><item><title>Fixing a Hole</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/fixing-a-hole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 22:04:53 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/fixing-a-hole/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m fixing a hole where the rain gets in&amp;hellip;
I&amp;rsquo;m sure this rotted out due to a poor decision from the factory of filling in weep hole with body filler or panel glue. On the side that was not completely disintegrated there was a bunch of goop in the corner in between the panels.
I regret starting with such a complex panel as the first one. I&amp;rsquo;ve had to remake the panel a few times before getting it &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Fixtures and Jigs</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/fixtures-and-jigs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 21:53:48 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/fixtures-and-jigs/</guid><description>After getting a better look at the chassis I realized that putting it onto a rotisserie would be a bad idea. The issue is the flex in the chassis, there is no way to guarantee that the chassis will not flex and move as as I cut out large section of the firewall and rockers.
So I decided to make a jig that bolts into some primary locations on th chassis and allows for some adjustment to ensure that everything is level.</description></item><item><title>A Fast Start</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/a-fast-start/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:59:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/a-fast-start/</guid><description>I started working on the white chassis. As the car sits in front of me I&amp;rsquo;ve pulled apart the: suspension (front and rear), interior dash, and interior sound deadening. Sound deadening took around 4 hours of chiselling while using dry ice to harden the old tar mat.
Most of the rust damage to the car is isolated to the battery tray. Probably due to battery acid eating the paint, then road salt and water damage over the years.</description></item><item><title>minimal wiring</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/minimal-wiring/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 22:05:29 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/minimal-wiring/</guid><description>California state law requires that cars sold after 75&amp;rsquo; have to pass a smog test in order to renew it&amp;rsquo;s registration. So what happens when you want to swap a motor into one of these newer cars?
Buddy if you went there then you buy a parts car, that has the engine that you want, so you can pull off all the required parts to get it BAR&amp;rsquo;d (approved by the state).</description></item><item><title>shadowed issues</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/shadowed-issues/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 23:38:49 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/shadowed-issues/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always better to know what the issue at hand is, and to turn off the alert for this issue, so that other issues can be observed. This is true for most types of engineering, my observations has been with race-cars, and software.
The RSX always had a check engine light for a gas-cap leak (fixed with a new seal), but I failed address the issue right away. Had I addressed the issue, I would have known that I was also throwing codes on the racetrack for a VTEC solenoid (oil probably), and a knock sensor failure (bye-bye motor), when I was on the race track.</description></item><item><title>Side Tracked</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/side-tracked/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 09:47:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/side-tracked/</guid><description>Side Tracked? Look-look-look, I just got a little side tracked with the side yard. There are still things that need to get shuffled around. But I had a terrible idea while out there the other night.
Fixating on the jacks for some reason, I decided right then and there that they were going to have to be lifted off the ground. So we looked online, and decided $89 was too much for a product like this, and that we could design one ourselves.</description></item><item><title>preparations</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/preparations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:48:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/preparations/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Preparations&amp;rdquo;, or how I cleaned the garage I&amp;rsquo;ve been working for several days on cleaning the garage in effort to make a revitalize the work space for restoration work. This includes cleaning the attic for part organization/storage, building new shelves in the shed (more parts storage), and reorganizing boxes on the shop floor.
Organization is not only for my mental sanity, its also a political move to keep everyone happy. If we were working in a mess, there would be additional &amp;ldquo;conversations&amp;rdquo; to be had about how the place is upside-down.</description></item><item><title>doctests</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/doctests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 18:48:23 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/doctests/</guid><description>Consider some small function such as:
def parse_string(input: str): try: name, value = input.split(&amp;#39;:&amp;#39;) except ValueError: name = input value = None assert name, input return name, value These utility functions typically have a small footprint, yet there can be dozens of them scattered in a codebase. Testing them directly within the test suite can be done, but if you start adding multiple files for multiple utility functions, the disassociation between proximity of definition and location of tests make it annoying to maintain.</description></item><item><title>how to make a cut</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/how-to-make-a-cut/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/how-to-make-a-cut/</guid><description>Sometimes you have to be technical with how you approach your cut, going in with your saw blazing mates it difficult to put things back together.
![[assembled.jpeg]]
My approach has been the following;
Clean back as much as possible to expose how the joints are formed. Make a mental model of what I need to replace (there is a lot in this case) Drill reassembly holes for Cleo fasteners Remove spot welds (punch, drill, spot weld cutter) Remove panels I ended up exposing the large section that I need to remove.</description></item></channel></rss>