<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>s30 on amar</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/tags/s30/</link><description>Recent content in s30 on amar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:59:44 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amarjandu.github.io/tags/s30/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Fast Start</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/s30/a-fast-start/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 17:59:44 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/s30/a-fast-start/</guid><description>I started working on the white chassis. As the car sits in front of me I&amp;rsquo;ve pulled apart the: suspension (front and rear), interior dash, and interior sound deadening. Sound deadening took around 4 hours of chiselling while using dry ice to harden the old tar mat.
Most of the rust damage to the car is isolated to the battery tray. Probably due to battery acid eating the paint, then road salt and water damage over the years.</description></item><item><title>Side Tracked</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/s30/side-tracked/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 09:47:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/s30/side-tracked/</guid><description>Side Tracked? Look-look-look, I just got a little side tracked with the side yard. There are still things that need to get shuffled around. But I had a terrible idea while out there the other night.
Fixating on the jacks for some reason, I decided right then and there that they were going to have to be lifted off the ground. So we looked online, and decided $89 was too much for a product like this, and that we could design one ourselves.</description></item><item><title>preparations</title><link>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/s30/preparations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:48:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://amarjandu.github.io/posts/s30/preparations/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Preparations&amp;rdquo;, or how I cleaned the garage I&amp;rsquo;ve been working for several days on cleaning the garage in effort to make a revitalize the work space for restoration work. This includes cleaning the attic for part organization/storage, building new shelves in the shed (more parts storage), and reorganizing boxes on the shop floor.
Organization is not only for my mental sanity, its also a political move to keep everyone happy. If we were working in a mess, there would be additional &amp;ldquo;conversations&amp;rdquo; to be had about how the place is upside-down.</description></item></channel></rss>